我梦见一个白色的圣诞
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
就像我以前度过的那样
Just like the ones I used to know.
树梢银光闪闪
Where the treetops glisten
儿童听着
And children listen
远处雪地里传来的雪橇铃声
To hear sleigh bells in the snow
我梦见一个白色的圣诞
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
就如我在每张圣诞贺卡上写的那样
With every Christmas card I write
希望你合家欢落 万事如玉
May your days be merry and bright
也祝你每个圣诞节都如此愉快
And may all your Christmases be white
我梦见一个白色的圣诞
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
就像我以前度过的那样
Just like the ones I used to know
树梢银光闪闪
Where the treetops glisten
儿童听着
And children listen
远处雪地里传来的雪橇铃声
To hear sleigh bells in the snow
我梦见一个白色的圣诞
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
就如我在每张圣诞贺卡上写的那样
With every Christmas card I write
祝你活家欢落 万似如意
May your days be merry and bright
也祝你每个圣诞节
And may all your Christmases be
祝你每个圣诞节
May all your Christmases be
都如此愉快
White